Heroes Retirement
If the heroes who saved the world could
find peace, their missions would be over.
However, those heroes were denounced and
set to be killed by the people they once saved.
People who said they had no more use for titans with extreme power.
But that was wrong.
Heroes who had achieved legendary deeds
shouldn't have had to die such brutal deaths.
If they were to be killed
when they were still heroes,
then they ought to
return to being regular citizens.
Helping heroes become normal citizens:
that was the job of the Hero Retirement and
Return to Everyday Life Assistance Agency.
Twin heroes?
Yeah.
Sisters, who were
dispatched as heroes together,
worked together, and returned together.
Really? That's quite something.
The older sister's name is Tsuranari Hakua.
The younger sister is Kougyoku.
Which will I be taking care of?
Tsuranari Hakua
Big sister : Main character
Tsuranari Kougyoku
Little sister : Donor
Twins
mori
donor
witch
raised in...
Big sister : Main character
Tsuranari Hakua
The older sister? The younger sister?
Both.
Both?
Yeah.
Since this is such a rare case, we decided to
have them transition to normal life together.
Giving you, Uro, this dangerous job,
was a unanimous decision.
Do the higher-ups think it's okay
to just give me any job they want?
You can't refuse or
talk your way out of this one.
I'd at least like an apology.
Which means that from now on,
you two will be living here
on Earth as regular citizens.
Do you have any questions?
"Do you have any questions", he says.
First you ought to bow down, peasant!
It's rude of you to speak
on the same eye level as I.
I've said this over and over. You are no longer a hero, but an ordinary person.
From here on out, you'll study and work like everyone else.
Calling a lady knight
"ordinary" is most irritating.
If I am ordinary, then what
do you suppose you are? A worm?
Or rubbish, perhaps?
I will not change!
Defiant, I see.
Well, kids like you
adapt quickly to everyday life.
Heh. Impossible.
That I would mingle with
commoners is unthinkable.
Is is not, sister of mine?
Surrounded with the sword,
armor, and ornaments I made,
my sister will forever stand as a hero...
She won't change.
Of that I am sure.
I'm home!!!
Ah, today work was tiring!
I worked soooo hard!
Uro, make dinner!
Good work.
Recently you've been doing full shifts every day.
I have to build up experience
quickly so I can level up my skills!
I can't keep being a bother to the shop manager forever.
How admirable of you.
And with me there, the atmosphere of the shop has improved, so I can rise quickly.
Really?
And there is something I want.
I should be able to get it
if I save up just a little more.
Don't work yourself too hard.
You're just an ordinary person now—
Ah, I'm tired of hearing that!
It's just a matter of time. They say it's good to keep a goal in mind.
Oh, sister of mine.
Do you want to hear my talk?
What do you think you're doing?
Where's your pride as a hero?
What are you getting so upset about?
It's not as though I can avoid
rubbing shoulders with the masses,
but that doesn't mean
I have given up my pride.
On the way home from work at the café,
I got a little cake so cutesy you'd squeal!
I don't understand... what are you saying?
And what's with that ordinary outfit?
Where's the silver armor I gave you?
No, no, no, I'd feel out of place wearing that!
Why don't you try being fashionable?
There's tons of cute clothing in this world.
That's right.
Kougyoku, you should join us next time we—
Shut up!
What about the sword?
The sword I gave you!
Eh? Don't you know?
The earth has this legal system.
They'll arrest you if you
have a blade over 6 cm long.
A law?
And gems?
What about the ruby in which I instilled divine protection?
If I wore that it would get stolen!
That would be dangerous.
I won't get shot, so don't worry!
And anyway, there's no
such thing as demons in this world,
so I don't need divine protection.
You're not my sister anymore.
Wait, Kougyoku.
What do you want?
Take off that eyepatch.
I know you can actually see.
It's probably dangerous to
not have depth perception.
Shut up!
What's up with that attitude?
Uro, hurry up and make dinner.
And the floor's sopping wet! Wipe that up!
Aren't you going to eat dinner?
You don't like ginger roast?
It's delicious.
Are you making a weapon?
Something wrong with that?
No, that's what you've
been doing your whole life.
The days keep coming, and you keep working in your studio,
making weapons and
armor and protective ornaments.
All for Hakua.
Hey, wasn't it hard for you?
That no matter how much work you put into the weapons,
the only one who received the honor and praise was the hero Hakua?
That's...
Even though you're the
one who gave Hakua her power,
no one paid any attention to you.
You just keep giving, but you can't get anything in return.
That's the fate of a supporting character.
When the crowds speak of Hakua,
my swords and armor are included.
That is my pride.
I don't need any reward.
And that's exactly why it's so hard
for me to forgive Hakua for changing.
Tossing away the things
I've made so carefully,
for some "part-time job", for some "fashion"!
Why are you changing my Hakua?
Yamada Uro!
That's my job.
Just like you made Hakua into a hero,
I'll make you two into regular citizens.
I won't change!
Of that I am sure.
And I'll show you,
and make Hakua a hero again!
Hey, that sword's all bent.
That's proof you're not looking at what's in front of your eyes.
You can't make a weapon that way.
Unlike the world you want to be in,
you can't easily use magic here.
If you want to become a craftsperson in this world, it'd be best to start from scratch—
If I use it that way, it's a weapon.
Hmph!
Uh... huh.
Bar     District
Tsuranari Kougyoku. Former craftsperson.
Item-maker who used all of her
power for her older sister, a hero.
It seems like she's still trapped in a dream.
And that dream is probably...
Why are you looking so gloomy?
You can't forgive the world that takes
the sister that she gave her all to,
and turns her into something mediocre, isn't she just the model younger sister?
Ahh, how innocent...
Having dreams is an admirable thing.
But I'd like if she'd stop having her dreams depend on another person.
I can't believe she's entrusting her
entire worth as a person to her sister...
She's a fool.
Do you think we should try to arrange a little get-together?
Get-together?
Assemble Alice and the heroes you've worked with so far at the beach,
and let Kougyoku-chan meet
someone other than Hakua-san.
You can count on me to be there to help.
That's a pretty good idea,
but you're not just asking because
you want to see girls in swimsuits, are you?
I refuse to confirm or deny my motivations.
Don't try and hide your fetishes.
We'll relax on the beach in the afternoon, and have barbecue for dinner.
Then, with full stomachs,
we'll have fun with fireworks.
It's a good chance for you to get to know each other better.
Hakua, Kyogyoku, say hello.
Aye.
To be honest, I thought this was a pain,
but as long as I'm here I plan to have fun.
I'm counting on you all.
Come on, you too, say hello.
Wow, I bet it'll be a lot of fun!
I can't wait to eat some barbecue!
Karon-san's as energetic as ever!
But to be sure, this is a great chance for us to
meet new people and strengthen our relationships.
Don't you think? Airo-san.
Not really.
If I have to say one way or the other, this feels like a bother to me.
I hate the heat.
Little one, remember to
play nice with your friends.
Since when have you been my mother, Alice?
Oh my. You don’t have to call me your mother, "young lady" will do fine.
Take this!
Killer technique,
Ultra No-Way-In-Hell Super Spike!
With an exceedingly lame attack name like that, there's no way you could defeat me, Karon!
Which means, it's my turn!
Miracle Hyper Jump-Powered Smash!
Alright, I did it!
To think I couldn't stop it at this range...
Working part-time all night might be hard,
but I haven't felt this kind of indignity since I was a hero!
How irritating!
Working part-time all night sure is hard.
When you're tired,
you can't summon any strength.
However. That physical
limitation is a good thing!
Striving to reach new heights,
dealing with a body that refuses to do as it's told...
Yes, yes, your will may be broken harder than your body in the end, but even so!
Buckling down and refusing to give in
creates its own kind of
light at the end of the tunnel!
Things aren't going to go as you expect.
But it's because you can't reach
those heights that life is interesting!
At first glance, you seemed dim-witted,
and your speech appeared foolishly blunt,
but you say can some rather deep things.
I don't mind if you start looking up to me.
I may be impertinent
and arrogant, but I like you.
Now that we're friends, why don't we run off into the sunset together?!
It's midday as hell right now, but I concur!
Where did they learn that kind of meat-headed communication?
Honestly, just looking at them is sweltering.
My, my, isn't it a good thing?
Blending bodies and heat,
their hearts move as one.
That kind of communication is lovely!
I-If you say so...
Yes! Of course, I also love the quiet bonding we are sharing right now.
There are many ways of
interacting with other people.
After all, there are so
many people in this world!
Reca-san, you have such a big heart.
As one would expect of a former princess.
There are times where I can't quite say the same about myself
I know it's not good, but...
Wait.
Why are the decorations all Rococo?
Didn't we decide on a Gothic style?
Well, it's because I like swirly things!
Airo-san, you're too picky about your scenery!
Wh—what's that supposed to mean?
This kind of thing works out best when you stick to the plan!
My, my, if you get that upset about it,
you're just as bad as Karon-san!
You're absolutely mistaken!
I'll tell Uro-kun about this!
Hey, wouldn't you agree?
How would I know?
Beautiful former heroes
in swimsuits! And the ocean!
Is this paradise?
What a peaceful scene!
That's right, peaceful.
Apart from you being here.
She can't fit in with them, huh.
That girl... she reminds me a lot of how you were long ago.
Really?
Yes, she's just like you.
What are you saying?
Compared to Uro-san,
Kougyoku-chan is way, way cuter!
Four-eyes, you're getting on my nerves.
You want things that are important to you to remain important.
That's why you can't accept new things.
You become obstinate and close in on yourself.
That's just like you!
You can say she's like me, but you shouldn't treat her that way.
Yes, I know that.
I won't tease her.
Well, maybe just a little.
It does make me want to... stir things up.
Everything tastes better
when you eat outside!
Uro, more alcohol.
You're drinking too much.
Kougyoku-san!
Perfectly-done meat, just for you!
The truth is, I've been aiming to talk to you since this afternoon,
but I became too caught
up frolicking with Hakua-san.
Kougyoku-san, let's be friends too!
What a pain.
Woah, rejected! I just got hit with a clear, outright rejection!
This time, it was your own fault.
Honestly, heroes sure have such bad manners, it's a problem.
Woah, from the witch too!
Let this loud one be,
and let's relax and talk over there, just us two support characters.
You're a pain too.
Oi, Kougyoku!
Stop it already! You've
got to try to communicate or—
Shut up!
What do you mean, "friends"?
What do you mean, "communication"?
Why do you get along with them?!
You're a hero, aren't you?!
What have you been so
unhappy about this whole time?
Everyone's going out of their way to have fun.
That's it! It's because of that that you're—
I have no idea what
my younger sister is thinking.
I'm going to check on her.
Okay.
Kougyoku-san!
Where are you?
Seriously, where could she have gone?
Alice went after her, so I'm sure it's nothing too extreme, but...
That is something to
be worried about, isn't it.
She's bound to be up to something,
that old monster.
She does tend to play
some nasty tricks sometimes.
She's overloaded with cuteness.
Kougyoku-san!
Hey, Uro-kun.
I hope Kougyoku-san won't be too mad at us.
Airo?
I kind of understand her feelings.
As support characters, no matter how hard we try, we can't get the glory.
That's why we get so
picky about certain things.
What's really important to her is probably...
Don't worry. She won't be mad.
I'm sure Hakua understands that too.
But where could Kougyoku-san be—
Honestly.
What could she possibly be
talking about, that sister of mine?
All my plans have gone down the drain!
Hakua!
I finished a new gem!
It's full of protection!
As long as you have this, you're invincible!
Good grief, she's so troublesome!
Kougyoku-san!
We still can't find her...
And where did that meat-head go?
And four-eyes, too.
If Karon-san's gone too, then that means...
Well, it is Alice.
Airo-san?
This is bad! Reca! Stay close to me!
Alice! Kougyoku!
I know you're there!
"We have the heroes. If you want them back, come to the beach!"
Yamada Uro!
Send Hakua and me back to our world!
Alice. What's this about?
Just helping out a woman
with something to say.
I'm here to test you, anytime, anywhere.
I don't suppose I could get you to
stop putting my life on Hard Mode?
Don't ignore me!
Send us back immediately!
Hey, Kougyoku. You made that
crossbow by yourself, didn't you.
You can't shoot with that.
It's not held together well, and it's crooked.
I'm sorry, but as long as
you can't accept this world,
you can't craft anything.
Shut up!
What right do you have to say such a thing?
Crafting things in this
world is a very difficult thing.
As long as you're not looking
properly at the things in front of you,
you can't make anything.
Why?
Why do you get in my way?
I just love the hero Hakua,
I want to make things for her
so she can be praised,
and free, and strong... that's all.
You stupid little sister!
Become the greatest craftsperson in this world,
too! This time, without any magic!
Kougyoku!
Hakua...
I was planning for a situation
where you were more excited,
but that's not a big deal anymore.
Here. It's a present for you.
Why...
Hakua's been working so hard at her part-time job to buy this for you.
Day in and day out, living a life she couldn't get used to...
Well, I can do anything if I put my mind to it.
Why...
why would you do something like that for me?
I'm a supporting character.
It's my job to give you—
What are you being so
picky about? Sister of mine.
I received so much from
you back in the other world.
This time it's my turn to give.
Earn money through dealing with people.
I'll take on the daily tasks of a hero.
That way you can put your whole
heart into mastering craftsmanship.
But that means you—
Who do you think I am?
In the other world
I was one of the greatest hero.
And in this world...
I'm your only sister.
And—
Woah!
you ought to be a little fashionable too.
Just like me, you can't
let your beauty go to waste.
Onee-chan...
Onee-chan!
Give me a sparkler!
Me too!
Come on, wait your turn!
That girl's just like you after all.
You keep saying that, but in what way?
Whenever she decides something's important, she won't let go no matter what happens.
Yes, very stubborn.
Ah, when you put it that way, I kind of—
Hey, Karon! Don't wave the
sparkler around! That's dangerous!
Somebody let me down...
With that matter settled, it's so much fun to fireworks with everyone!
You were easily captured
pretty early on, weren't you?
You sure are the kind of witch that little kids worry about.
What did you say?
Let's light up one more!
Hey, wait!
Oh, I lost again!
Yay, seven wins in a row!
That's my little sister!
I won't lose the next one!
I'll win the next one too!
That'll make eight points!
What a nice breeze.
Don't you think there are
beautiful things in this world, too?
Yes!
Kagayaita hibi no ichi PEEJI
A page of the brilliant everyday
boku no asu wo uranau
predicts my tomorrow.
Dareka ga kureru gensou wa awa to kieta
The illusion someone gave me disappears in a mist.
Doko ni iru ka mo wakaranai you na
I wander within dull scenery
iroaseta keshiki no naka samayou
as if I don’t know where I am anymore.
Kasuka na hikari chiisana inori
I’m always the only one
mamoreru no wa itsumo jibun dake dakara
who can protect the faint light and small hope.
Haruka oka de utau omoi wa
I wonder if memories of singing on a distant hill
toki no hate ni todoku no kana
will last until the end of time.
Shines like a diamond
Isshun no kirameki
A sudden flash
migaita hikari ga shimesu no wa ah boku ga shiranai mirai
of a bright light shows my unknown future.